[music]
[singing]
>> All right, ladies and gentlemen. It's
currently January 16th.
Now, you're probably watching this
sometime into February. You know why?
Cuz I already [__] streaked the Super
Bowl. So, you're probably wondering,
"What is What are What are we doing
here? What's going on? Why are you a
month before in a stadium in a football
field?"
>> [sighs]
>> Because I'm training.
This is a joke. You think I'm going to
pay $100,000 for Super Bowl tickets to
not successfully make it onto the field
and be over 60 seconds on the field?
That's the bet that I have with my boys
going on right now. There's no doubt
that I'm streaking the Super Bowl. The
doubt is, am I going to make it more
than 60 seconds?
And I'm out of breath. So, I'm I'm here
training every single day. One, I'm
training how I'm going to run when I get
onto the field. How I'm going to
do this, right? I'm doing it already
with the shoes that I'm going to run
with.
So, last time that we streaked the Super
Bowl, we almost got caught because of
our shoes. These are much more low-key
shoes with cleats.
And last time I wasn't prepared. I got
tired. The adrenaline I hadn't ran that
fast in a long time.
>> And last time it was a last-minute
decision. It was like a 48-hour decision
that we decided to do. Now, I've been
prepping for this for nearly a month. I
remember last year, I literally went
like this to one dude, just like a small
step. Boom.
The dude in the yellow security was
like,
he fell. You guys also have to like
remember, you have to put yourself into
the perspective of these security guys.
One, they're not expecting someone to
run. Two, they've been standing for two,
three hours. So, their back is tight,
their knees are tight, and I'm going to
go warmed up. I'm going to go ready to
go. When I get on the field and I hit a
minor juke on them, they're so cold and
so tight that they just It's impossible
for them to catch up to me. Especially
Look at me, I'm [__] diesel.
Look at this.
It's 190 lb of pure [__] Cuban
muscle.
Look at that. You think they're going to
catch me?
You know, it'd be a total fail if I get
tackled in the first two feet.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, that'd suck.
>> That would really suck. That would be
pretty embarrassing. I don't think
that's going to happen. But just know
that we're making it onto the field.
It's a matter of if we're going to be
over or under 60 seconds. 60 seconds is
a long time, dude.
>> Hopefully this time we get airtime.
>> Yeah.
>> Dude, we got a streaker on the other
>> I was thinking about it.
Might tackle a football player, might
not. Depends how I feel.
>> Or they might tackle you.
>> Come on. COME ON.
>> THEY'RE DEFINITELY NOT GOING TO TACKLE
US.
>> INCOMING.
>> Tackle him.
>> Then they're going to hit the same on
you. You know, reverse.
>> Some of you guys may be wondering why am
I going to do this?
The simple answer is
why the [__] not?
That's it.
Why not?
>> It'll be my third time in jail. How
about you?
>> Again, thanks to you, I haven't gone to
jail.
>> These are the mugshots for Alex Gonzalez
and Sebastian Rivera.
>> Now I'm going to go twice.
>> Rookie numbers. Get those numbers up,
boy.
>> Rookie numbers.
>> Honestly, I don't I don't do drugs. I
don't drink. Rarely ever drink. I don't
do anything to not be sober.
>> The adrenaline that I got when I did
that is unexplainable. I blacked out. I
don't remember what happened and I'm
chasing that high once again. The
feeling of doing the impossible. I love
this right here. Game planning,
logistics, doing what nobody's going to
think that's going to go down. We're
going to do it. You know, we're going to
post like if we're going to be in Hawaii
or something, right? Cuz I think they're
going to be watching our stories on
Instagram. I'm going to be posting like
if I'm in a different country. There's
just so many steps to this that people
don't understand. They just think we
just go to the field and run. No,
there's a whole preparation. Like
>> I'm here training. My trainer's pulling
up right now with the cones. My goal is
to succeed. I'm not just doing this to
[__] it do it. If I'm going to do it,
I'm going to do it right. My goal, 60
seconds over, at least juke two. I even
juked you right there. You saw that?
>> You juked the camera, not me.
>> I juked the camera. And if I can jump
over somebody, that should brownie
points. We got something big coming,
something very big.
Athena. You guys don't know what Athena
is, don't worry. You're going to see it
here. I'm taking promotions, promos. So
we're going to run and we're going to
have of on us. Athena.com or whatever
the domain is that we decided at time.
It's a it's a trading tool, the software
that basically trades for you without
actually trading for you. It finds the
highest probability trade setups, shows
you the confluences, shows you what the
trade has, shows you what it doesn't
have, and it grades the trade for you.
And at that point you can decide to take
it or go to another trade that has a
higher probability. It has a
leaderboard, journals the trades for
you, everything, so many things. So, and
this run this streak is going to be the
launch of the registration to get access
to Athena.
>> [snorts]
>> So, there's also a little bit of a idea
behind this as well. So,
Yeah. Want to know?
Warming up.
>> Yo, you got to train also, bro. I bet
you money you can't even touch me right
now if you wanted to.
>> I think I could touch you, but no shot.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> That's exactly what's going to happen,
bro. All right, so we got my trainer
here, Mac.
What do you Yo, so we got 3 weeks before
we actually do this [__] What do you
What do you think?
>> I mean, we're going to work on getting a
little quicker, you know, more agile,
side to side. We're going to work on
some lateral movements.
>> Also, you're out of shape, bro. You
think you're faster than me?
>> Let's race.
>> We could do like a simulation after we
run a couple drills.
>> What, I try to catch you?
>> Yeah, you have to try and tag. It's
literally like a tag.
>> Okay, yeah.
>> it with him, he couldn't tag me.
>> I'm down, I'm down.
>> You won't tag me, no shot.
>> All right. You want to do a straight
>> No, I
I'm just going to free like free it.
>> No, I just want to see who I'm faster
than you.
>> You're probably faster than me on a
straight, but I'm down. I'm down.
[laughter]
>> I'm down, I'm down.
>> but I know, but I know.
>> All right, all right. All right, we got
3 weeks, 3 [__] weeks.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music and singing]
>> easy.
Look at this. Way better.
>> One.
Go.
No,
>> [laughter]
>> I don't want to.
>> Yeah?
>> you took those little steps?
>> Yeah.
>> So, that's what you should do. You
should take those little steps so you
can gather your feet. So, you're not
lost. So, when you stop, you can stop so
you can press.
You get me? But, make those little steps
fast. Don't make them like, "Oh, I got
to slow down." Chop your feet. Shuffle
your feet. Go.
Like, right now, I'll smoke you just
because you don't have cleats on.
>> 100%.
>> And, bro, 90% of those guys
>> don't have cleats on.
>> 100% I don't have cleats.
>> I'll be honest with you. If I can't
catch you right now, let's try it.
They're not catching you.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. So, they're definitely not
catching you.
>> Bro, they're not catching me. I promise.
>> They're going to come out of my cleats.
>> Go.
>> Ooh, GOT HIS ASS.
>> [laughter]
>> THE CLEATS MAKE A DIFFERENCE, BRO.
>> [__] THE CLEATS MAKE A big ass
difference. I'm not even playing, bro.
>> We have the cleats as our advantage, the
sneak attack, plus the decoys, and we're
training. It's a wrap.
>> Yeah.
>> And, he's training with me, so he'll be
all right.
>> And, we've been training with Mac.
>> It's the method.
>> The problem is that 60 seconds is a long
time.
>> It is. And, remember, it's one of you
versus 10 of them.
>> Yeah.
>> I said disadvantage.
>> Like, I'll catch Salas in 2 seconds.
>> All right. Three.
Two. Go.
All right. Let's do a straight line.
Let's see what we got. I want to see how
close I get with no cleats.
>> Okay.
>> Go.
One. Go.
>> Oh, yeah. Too easy, my boy.
>> Who won that?
>> Mac.
Crazy, huh? I only said 100 grand. He
wanted to do 200. Bro, let me get some
cleats. Let me get some cleats.
All right.
Three weeks away, baby. Yo, is that your
trainer if he doesn't beat you?
>> [snorts]
>> Well, we're here again.
>> [laughter]
>> You You know You know what's crazy? So,
I've been like 2 days plotting this
[__] right? Like I've done my due
diligence. I've been studying the field.
The The problem is that there's no
tickets available. There has to be some
type of solution. No, no, no.
>> [laughter]
>> Further, there is a solution. And it's
buying these tickets right here.
It's buying these tickets on row one
for $100,000.
>> [laughter]
>> God.
Look Look Look at this picture, right?
This is what I love about SeatGeek. This
These are These are the seats right
here. These are $100,000 tickets right
here. You're literally Like this is
exactly what I need. Brother, that is
like That's easier than the first time
around. Brother, that that that is it.
The thing is that if I were to go get
two tickets right now for you and I
Look at this. Right here. We come here.
I go to two tickets. I click continue.
Plus the fee at this [__] platform
charges. It's going to be $220,000.
We I think we can
>> [laughter]
>> I can think of so many things we can use
that money for. I know, but just think
about it, bro. It's just let Like that
right there, us getting those tickets is
a lock. We're on the field 100%. Oh, and
another thing. This is another side
note. Bro, we can't wear those cleats.
The stairs are white. So, those cleats
you're going to be able to very clearly
see that they're cleats when we're going
up and down. So, we need to get
different different cleats. I I really
don't want to spend $220,000 on [__]
Super Bowl tickets. And the problem is
that I've been checking this out every
single day for the last week. Look,
right now it's currently January 19th.
So, we're about 19 days away, right?
Roughly or whatever the time is for the
Super Bowl. And the prices aren't going
down, and more tickets are not being
available. We got our tickets last time
with like 48 Not even 24 hours, right?
Maybe we got lucky. Maybe we got lucky,
but I need to lock this in now. I can
buy this ticket for 100 grand, right?
And then I can get you one like up here
for
What? The cheapest one is like $9,000,
bro. I can get you one here for $9,000
and or this one for $7,000 in the
nosebleeds.
And then somehow we sneak you in down
here. And once you make it down here,
then we just figure it out or like you
just like rush, respectfully, right?
Homie, this physique, you are not faster
or stronger than me. This guy with
shades will never see it coming. A girl
stands no chance.
Fatty over here is just not happening.
None of these people are qualified to
remotely keep up with me. They're not
wearing cleats. I'm going to
zook them, bro.
I'm so confident in myself. With with
with this lineup right here,
>> [laughter]
>> we're on that field 100%. I'm going to
do a little bit more of my research and
I'll get back to you guys. But right now
it's looking like $100,000. 1 week, 2
weeks, 14 days, 15, 16, 17, 18 days,
ladies and gentlemen. And I think we
have found our tickets for the Super
Bowl. Patience pays. Look at this [__]
As you guys can see earlier when we were
looking at these tickets, remember how
there was like no tickets available?
Look at it now. So many more tickets
available everywhere. And we got our
tickets right here. We have row 1, row
2, row 3. 13,000, 30,000, and 18,000
dollars per ticket. We have a executive
decision to make on which one of these
three sections do we sit on? Obviously,
they're all in the front, which is good.
We have section 1, section 2, section 3,
all row 1. So, if I were to look at
these tickets for example, we're
literally the first people like we're
right in front. Like we are row 1. So, I
like this one because it's more of a
open, right? So, we can go from here and
then we can decide if we go this way or
this way or just straight down the
middle, which is where we were last
time. We were just on this side last
time. Now, we have another problem. We
can't get these tickets under my name
because last time I bought the tickets
under my name and uh
>> We might be flagged.
>> Yeah, we might uh pop up as a big red
flag. They might notify the Super Bowl.
It's like, "Hey, just uh NFL, just
letting you know you have a repeating
offenders going to the Super Bowl." Uh
and coincidentally enough they're
sitting in the exact same spot they did
it last time in the first row.
So, just uh be on the lookout.
So, we're going to buy tickets under
somebody else's name with a different
credit card, everything completely
different. So, look, section 123, row
one, $18,000 per ticket. Bro, SeatGeek
should like promote us, bro.
>> [laughter]
>> They're seeking promotion right there.
>> Dude, what the [__] man?
>> Okay, so I just created a new identity,
a new profile. So, the total is 37,100
and $12.
And the beauty of this is I'm not paying
for it. I'm using my friend's credit
card. Uh thanks, Sensei. Shout out to
Sensei for giving me his credit card.
There you guys can see.
Pay now.
Shout out to Sebastian's for using
Sebastian's [__] credit card. Total
is $37,000.
All right, so we just click pay now.
Your tickets have been confirmed, ladies
and gentlemen. Section 123, row one.
Congrats, now there's no way we're going
back.
Now there's no turning back.
>> [__] turning back from this point,
bro.
>> Hey,
see you on the other side. Try and catch
up.
>> Well, I'll see you in jail.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah, this time
I'm going to eat a lot more before I go
in. We were in there for a lot longer
than I expected. So, I'm going to
actually make sure to eat before. Well,
I can't eat too much because I have to
run fast, so I can't be full.
>> We got to make sure we use the bathroom.
>> Yes, we have to use the bathroom.
>> First, before we do anything.
>> [__] pee myself again.
>> All right, we're live. Well, we're
18 days away.
Time for some more training.
>> I'm [__] ready.
>> Ladies and gentlemen, we are 24 hours
away from uh uh more like 28 hours away
from going to jail. So, you guys know
I'm I'm very superstitious. Last time we
successfully streaked the Super Bowl, we
came to the local dicks of that state.
Prep got prepared. What was it the same
day or the day before?
>> That was like literally an hour before
the actual
>> An hour before the Super Bowl, right?
>> Yeah. Uh dude, but there's nothing wrong
with being early.
>> You sure? Well, so right now we're on
our way to the dick. We need a disguise.
We need new cleats just in case. There's
better ones here. And we need Oh, the
Sharpies so we can draw on ourselves our
big message for the event.
>> This time we could do it more
professional on a better
>> Yeah, I know, bro. We did that [__] in
the bathroom of the dicks. Remember, we
might have to do it again in the
bathroom of the dicks, bro.
>> These are actually pretty good. These
are actually the first my first time
seeing kind of ones
>> Yeah, those are baseball turf ones are
good.
Um
>> We're playing on actual turf.
But it's got to be low low-key. Like
nobody can find out.
>> We bought like five pairs of shoes for
no reason.
>> Oh, bro, it's under $100. Oh, we we have
a rule of thumb. Anything under $100 is
technically
anywhere we go.
So, this is technically free. All right,
guys. So, so we're here. We're looking
for disguises right now. I think I'm
talking like I'm probably We're We're
about to do crime, but not like here.
Oh, when we got arrested in Vegas, in
the bottom, there was a picture of 15
people that the cops were just looking
for monitoring the whole entire time.
And then I overheard the cops where we
were in the cell in the stadium. They're
like, "Oh, we need to add both of these
guys to the list. Put them on the wall."
So, I'm sure they send all of these
images across the stadiums wherever the
Super Bowl is going to be. So, we need a
disguise.
It's my thought process right here,
right? Who Who's going to win? Is San
Francisco going to win or who's going to
win?
>> It's not San Francisco versus the
dolphins.
>> Who the [__] is playing?
>> [__] up. I'm not going to lie, you look
10 times more suspicious with the
glasses [laughter] and the hat and that
fit.
>> it look?
>> That looks way less suspicious.
>> Looks better, right? Or you want to see
how you look?
Go Seahawks.
>> And no one will to a thing.
>> Bro, we're going at different times,
bro. I think we're more than good.
>> Before we continue going forward, I just
got my contact with my attorney here in
San Francisco. Hey, how are you? It's
Alex. I got your number
>> Hi Alex, how are you? I just saw your
video from uh Vegas from 2 years ago,
your your special event that you did.
>> [laughter]
>> You know, hypothetically, let's say we
were to do something like that again.
>> Yes, hypothetically, yes.
Um
okay, so do you have like do you know
when you can do it?
>> Whenever the window of opportunity
presents itself. Like I got you know, we
didn't really aim for a specific quarter
to be honest, but we're trying You're
doing good. You sound young though. I
like older guys.
>> When it comes to the law.
>> When it comes to law. Like I I I've I've
had young attorneys.
One really good attorney, Wooster Law,
the guy's protecting me from my crashed
Bugatti. I've had a couple other
lawsuits. I've been sued multiple times.
>> You know you're successful when you
start getting sued a lot.
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
But we're still up though, right? [__]
>> Right, it's the jeans, right?
>> Why the [__] did they do a stadium after
a pair of jeans?
>> They got no [__] idea.
Who is pulling up right now?
>> [music]
[music]
>> Oh bro, I'm ready.
>> Big day, big crowd.
>> We got to practice once we pass the
security. Like what are we going to do?
Because I remember when I outrun that
security, I just I generally didn't know
what to do, so I just threw my hands up.
And then I just kept running straight to
the other side and just threw myself.
>> Yeah.
>> We can't have that.
>> That was a L in the chat. So we're going
to be something like this, just
chilling, watching the game, studying
the field, right? So we're literally
going to be this same distance from the
field. Look, Sean, listen.
So, I got to practice the off-mounting.
I feel like last time we did it so slow,
bro. Remember?
>> Well, however we did it, it worked. I
don't even remember doing it.
>> All right, ready?
And this is so you guys get an idea of
how high I'm jumping from. So, I'm 6'2".
>> 5'10".
>> So, this is probably actually like 6'2".
So, this is like realistic height from
what I remember. So, Sebas is going to
go right now.
>> Like here, I literally get blanked out.
>> Why?
>> Cuz I have no idea how I'm going to do
this.
>> The thing you got to do is how I do it.
You can't like jump over and stop. You
got to keep it going.
>> Let's go, Seacocks. Let's go.
>> Ah, that's how you're caught.
Too long. That's what I'm saying. You
You got to use like the all in one
motion.
>> I'm not confident to jump, but I'm
confident that whatever I end up doing
is going to work cuz if I made it work
the first time around
>> I know, brother, but we got to practice.
You're a lot heavier than last time.
>> Let's go, Seacocks. Let's [__] go.
>> Way too slow, bro.
You got caught.
So, the ghost to make it look
obviously fake, right? But, who the [__]
is paying again?
>> Bro, then you never be able to tell.
>> [laughter]
>> Our edge is the element of surprise and
having the freedom to state the obvious.
>> [laughter]
>> This is This is the costume.
>> This is perfect, Zach.
>> This is going to work 1,000%
[clears throat]
[laughter]
>> You think it's
>> 1,000% is going to work.
>> What if I wear this one?
>> I think that one's better. Big curly
beard, all right.
>> That just looks like a mess, bro.
Yeah, [__] This head not look good at
all. There's is bunch of pubic hair on
your face.
>> It feels [__] weird.
I hope nobody wore that on the field.
>> Yeah, brother, you totally passed, bro.
>> I passed as the Colombian Asian.
>> I feel like this works, bro. I feel like
it's going to state the obvious and
that's like the plan, right?
>> I think that's the point. I don't think
none of these are going to look real, so
we got to make it look fake.
>> Yeah.
>> Like very fakely obvious. And and
getting off the field, I'm just going to
like
>> yank it off, bro.
>> [laughter]
>> Imagine I hit the Steve and leave it on
when I take my mug shot.
>> so I'm going to call Vitaly, see what he
thinks about my disguise. I actually did
this because of Vitaly last time.
>> [laughter]
>> How's my disguise? Is my disguise?
>> Oh, you got the Super Bowl tomorrow?
>> Yeah, I'm here.
>> Bro, that's not your disguise. That's
what you dress up like if you're going
to streak the Super Bowl. That would not
work.
>> Dude, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, is this disguise good or no?
>> No, bro, you got money. I thought you
were going to have like a professional
Grandpa, like like people like Jackass
makeup, like five
>> The prob Yeah.
But I'm not I promise I'm not showing
it. The problem is that for like my mug
shot, I don't want to have that [__] on,
you know?
>> Oh,
oh [__] Okay, okay.
>> You know what? I I want to run on the
field and people know that it's me. I
feel like if I paint this blue and I'm
stating the obvious, I feel like it'll
it'll work, no?
>> No, it just looks like you're just a
party guy going. Yeah, yeah. Obviously
that you don't look real old man.
>> I mean, do you think this is good or no?
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> Are you sure? Like I'm I'm going to go
based off of what you tell me, bro.
>> What do you know? I'm going to be
responsible to get got out?
>> 100% bro, you're the guy. You're the
legend.
>> No, to be honest, it's completely [__]
>> [laughter]
>> You're running naked in the Super Bowl
game?
>> No, no.
>> No.
I'm hearing [__] bro. Well, good luck.
I'm going to be watching now. I can't
believe I forgot you told me you were
going to do it.
>> No, no. I got you. I have to I have to
>> Dude, I can see the straps.
>> That's the It's I'm supposed to state
the obvious. I'm going to paint it blue.
I'm going to paint the beard blue.
>> Yeah, yeah. It's like I think it's
honestly funnier if it's like kind of
obvious.
>> I think we're good.
It's game day, brother.
>> It is indeed.
>> You look like a completely different
person with those glasses.
>> Do I?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, bro. I'm looking at bro. Look at
this
FBI right there.
I don't even see it.
>> It ain't no joke.
>> Yeah, I know. To all my law enforcement
officers, I respect, I support law
enforcement, love law enforcement. I
actually studied criminal justice. I was
going to be a police officer. Didn't
work out. This is no disrespect to any
of you guys, but I will be juking you
guys today. I'm just more prepared in
terms of the element of surprise.
But, I don't condone this to anybody. I
don't believe anybody should be doing
this. I'm just doing it because I am
crazy, living on free will. And we've
been preparing this for some time. You
guys are preparing for safety to make
sure that everybody is safe. There's no
threats to the people of the stadium. I
am no threat to anybody of the stadium.
I am not endangering anybody.
I just have uh
a desire for high adrenaline moments,
and this is one of them. It's 10:00 in
the morning. We're right on schedule.
We're going to go buy Ray-Ban meta
glasses. And after that, we're going to
eat. We're going to go to the field,
warm up, stretch, train, come back,
shower, paint, straight in, prep.
Today's our That's our schedule today.
>> Very tight itinerary.
>> Very tight itinerary. I have nothing
other to say than
let the show begin, baby.
>> This is what I wanted to get a tattoo.
>> No.
>> Not at all, my brother.
>> Should we put the FouseyTube in the back
or in the front shirt?
>> I got a jersey. You should do
>> Oh.
>> FouseyTube Alex G, and then
>> Trey with the theme.
>> Yo, that's how I look from the back? Yo,
I got a big ass back, bro. Yo, I got a
big ass back. All right, I'm ready. I'm
ready for the real thing. My boy said
>> They weren't like from the back.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, yo. So, look. This was the
Sharpie that that we used earlier.
That's the other one, bro. I don't know
why like I tried to take it off, it
doesn't come off.
>> That's a big ass T, bro.
>> do it thick.
>> You're right, you're right. Go ahead.
>> [laughter]
>> Trading, where is trading right?
>> Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
>> I'm going to finish it, but I got to do
the T over here.
>> Wait, trade in the blind spot. We could
just do trade.
>> [laughter]
>> Bro, it looks sinister.
>> It looks like you're in a paranormal
activity movie, you know, the way they
wake up with all those scratches.
>> Really?
>> [clears throat]
>> I had that belly.
>> What is that?
>> This is the Super Bowl body where you
can see. [laughter]
>> We literally flew this guy out from
Miami just to come do this [__]
>> You know what the [__] is this?
>> [laughter]
>> What the [__] is this?
>> I was trying to do it with the same
confidence I did the other one. Hold on.
>> What the [__] man?
>> I said hold on.
>> Brother, you got to humble yourself.
>> [laughter]
>> This guy thinks he's Leonardo da Vinci
all of a sudden.
>> [snorts]
>> Stretching in here.
>> [__] why are you flexing? Look at how
that E came out now. Cuz you want to you
want to be you want to be Schwartz a
[__] in the MIDDLE OF IT.
>> CAN'T [__] CATCH ME, [__]
>> SEE THAT?
>> TRADE.
>> [laughter]
>> OH, too bad you look so when you did
that in the camera.
>> Trade.
With the Tina.
>> With is w i t h, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, boys. All right, let's go.
Game plan right now.
So, Sal is up first right now. So, we
just got our Russian spy right here. Our
Russian spy just went in, made it all
the way to the security point, no
issues, right?
>> No, no issues.
>> No issues? Okay, so he's in the clear.
Sal, you're going to go in now with your
mustache. Once you're in the stadium,
you give me the green light and then I
go.
>> Sounds good.
>> All right, go.
>> Who is this guy?
>> brother. Good luck.
>> Roger out. All right, so I am in the
middle of walking in.
As you can see,
I am in my disguise.
And now we're going to set up for game.
>> I just met up with Sal.
We had a little bit of an incident where
I was sweating coming in here because
it's so hot that some of the messaging
smeared. We just fixed it in the
bathroom. Little sus, but we got it
back.
>> Nobody saw us, so it's not sus at all.
>> Nobody saw us, now we're going to make
our way to our seats and start
>> scheming up. Big moments.
>> [music]
[cheering]
[music]
>> All right, so these are the only
This is the only obstacle we have right
there.
>> [music]
>> This is
We pass these guys
and it's done deal.
You got to make it far.
>> Looks like your team's cooked, buddy.
>> What's the bus going to be though?
>> Yo, what are we going to do with that
money?
>> You might as well.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Now is the time, huh?
>> [music]
[music]
>> I got this.
I got this.
>> [__] yeah.
LET'S GO.
>> [cheering]
>> COME ON.
COME ON. COME ON.
>> [music]
[cheering]
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS GOT ME?
YOU GUYS GOT ME? YOU GUYS GOT ME?
I'm right here. You guys got me?
We're going to
>> [music]
[music]
[laughter]
>> Oh, WE MADE IT OUT.
THAT WAS SO QUICK.
Uh
>> [laughter]
>> Bro, you have you have to turn on your
phone.
I got to see that video.
>> [laughter]
>> Bro, a lot of people at this point in
the video if you're still watching
probably wondering so why did you streak
the Super Bowl? I There's actually a
couple reasons, right? One of the
reasons is why the [__] not, right? Like
it was pretty fun if you ask me. The
adrenaline rush was crazy. Say less
without you, my brother.
>> It would have never happened.
>> Would have never happened. Brother, you
you you you did what nobody else would
have the balls to do, bro. You went on a
suicide mission and you completed it
successfully. So, thank you for that.
Uh without you the message would have
not been able to get transmitted to all
traders around the world, which is
trading in the blind spot is where
profitable trades are at. And some
people that don't know about trading
don't know what that means and I don't
care for them to understand because for
me [clears throat] 2026 I really wanted
to solve a problem for a lot of traders
and that's becoming profitable in the
most effective way. And that's by
finding the perfect trades and those
perfect trades are in the blind spot,
which is right in front of you. So, I
decided to create a solution for that,
which is Athena. So, that's why in the
back of my back I had trade with Athena.
Athena's a software solution that
literally finds these perfect trades for
you. It'll chart it up for you. It'll
identify where's a good trade to enter,
what's a bad trade to not enter, what
confluences it have, what confluences it
does not have for the perfect trade
setup so you can actually have a strong
trade or you can tell if it's a weak
trade. And uh yeah, I decided to just
tell everybody that probability is in
the blind spot and Athena is the
solution to that. So, this is uh
something that I'm only going to do like
probably once this one entire year.
And it was like creative way on how to
market it.
And uh it'll be open in what 21 days.
We're going to let some people get
access to it.
>> We'll be letting that out
>> Something like that.
>> Something like that. You guys want to
know more about it, link in the
description below. If you guys enjoyed
this video, since I know Seven cooked up
a crazy video, hit that like and
subscribe button.
And maybe you'll see us in 2027. Maybe
you won't. Maybe you'll see us at a
different event. If you got If you know,
you know.
But yeah, that's why we shot the Super
Bowl because we had a solution for all
of our traders that wanted to have an
advantage edge over everybody else. So
All I can say is Seven for Guap and I'll
see you guys in the next video.
>> And I say hell yeah. Hell yeah. Hell
yeah. [__] right.
[__] right. All right. And we say
hell yeah. Hell yeah. Hell yeah.
>> [music]
>> [__] right.
Hell yeah.
All right. And we say hell yeah.
[__] right.
And we say hell yeah.
Hell yeah.
[__] right.
Damn right. All right.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.